open up your authentic career
possibilities and NTT DATA MTT data is a
top 10 global IT services provider
operating in more than 50 countries NTT
DATA
is a human centric organization our
diverse workforce is our power of
innovation you will find various career
development opportunities in NTT DATA
and utilize your talents to make
positive contributions to society by
creating innovative IT services
solutions you will be able to sharpen
business technical expertise and
creative skills via on-the-job trainings
workshops and elearning platforms you
will also have access to NTT datas
unique business methodology and internal
certification systems to cultivate their
contribution to organizational power NTT
DATA works with local intimacy while at
the same time our qualified global
professional network of 130,000
employees is also one of our unique
strengths we have several global
leadership programs to enhance
collaboration at each stage of employees
in these programs participants are able
to enhance practical leadership
development through lectures from top
management intensive discussions and
collaborative business development
activities fostering international human
networks between executives and leaders
encourages mutual understandings and
innovative business ideas our leadership
program is focused on new up-and-coming
leaders I was lucky enough to have a
mentor that really saw more in me and
wanted me to grow the leadership program
is with solidified my reasoning for
staying identity MTT datas initiatives
to nurture our human power are
recognized in many countries and we have
gained a number of Human Resources
abilities join us
and meet our colleagues to share your
passion and imagination
[Music]